I don’t believe in God...
Ben Allaha inanmiyorum...
Everything came from the Big Bang...
Herşey "Big Bang"'den oluştu...
And the Bible was written by mortal men...
Ve Incil ölümlülerden yazılmıştır...
What the...? Oh, oh!
Ne bu...? Eyvah!
– Where am I?
- Nerede im?
– Where do you think you are?
- Nerede olduğunu düşünüyorsun?
– Who are you?
- Sen kimsin?
– I am the God of the Bible, the Creator of the universe.
- Ben Incilin tanrısı im, kainatın yaratıcısı.
You are here to be judged before Me!
Sen Benim önümde yargılanmak için burada sın!
– Am I in heaven?
- Ben cennet'de miyim?
– For the moment.
- Şimdilik.
According to My allknowing knowledge, you did not believe in Me, when you were alive.
Her şeyi bilen bilgime göre, Bana inanmamışsın hayatta iken.
Explain why. I need to know.
Nedeni açıkla. Bilmem gerekiyor.
– Errm, because... there was no evidence that you actually exist?
- Eeeem, çünkü... varolduğun için kanıt yokdu?
– No evidence?!
- Kanıt mı yokdu?
Did you ever hear of something called the Holy Bible??
Hiç Mukaddes İncil diye birşey'den duydun mu??
– Well, yeaah, but...
- Şey, evet, ama...
– “Yeah but” nothing!
- "Evet ama"'sı yok!
I wrote that book.
Ben o kitabı yazdım.
And if you had read it, you’d know that.
Ve eğer okusaydın, sen de bunu bilirdin.
Do you actually admit that you were an atheist?
Gerçekten ateist oluğunu itiraf mı ediyorsun?
– Well, yeah.
- Şey, evet.
– As I wrote in the Bible, the only way to salvation is through My son, Jesus Christ.
- İncil'de böyle buyuruyorum: kurtuluşun tek yolu Benim oğlum, İsa, ile dir.
– But I was a good person...
- Ama ben iyi bir insan idim...
I volunteered at a homeless shelter for like ten years.
Ben bir evsiz sığınağı'da yardım ettim, böyle on sene mi ne.
– It doesn’t matter! Did you or did you not worship Me, the God of the Bible?
- Bu önemsizdir! İncilin tanrısıyım, Bana ibadet ettin mi yada etmedin mi?
– Errrh, no...
- Eeeee, hayır...
– Wrong answer!! I created the universe, you should’ve worshiped and praised Me!
- Yanlış çevap!! Ben kainatı yarattım, Bana tapmalı ve Beni övmeli idin!
I’m not very happy about this!
Ben buna çok üzüntülü im!
– Isn’t that a little... petty of you?
- Bu senden biraz... dar kafalı değil mi?
– Silence!! My universe, My rules!
- Kes sesini! Benim kainatım, benim kurallarım!
– Ookaaay, how about if I start worshiping and praising you now?
- Pekiii, şindi seni tapmaya ve övmeye başlasam olurmu?
– Too late. You failed your test in life, and now you must face eternal consequences.
- Geç kaldın. Sen hayat imtihani başaramadın, ve şimdi ezeli cesanı çekmeli sin!
– Buut, I thought you were supposed to be all-merciful and all-forgiving...
- Amaa ben sandım sen rahman ve rahim sin.
– Only to people who believe that I exist.
- Sadece Benim varlığıma inananlara doğru.
Once I make someone die, a·and they see Me...
Insanin hayatını aldım mı, ve Beni görürlerse...
...they can’t change their mind!
...fikirlerini degiştiremezler!
Exactly how forgiving do you expect Me to be?
Nekadar bağışlayıcı olmamı bekliyorsun?
– Can you make an exception?
- İstisna yapabilirmisin?
I mean, I taught my children to be considerate and generous to others.
Yani, ben çocuklarıma saygılı ve cömert olmalarına öğrettim.
– NOOooo!!
- HAAayıır!!
What do you think heaven would be like if I let in every good person??
Cennet neye benzer, eğer her iyi kişiyi içere birakırsam??
– Errrhmm...
- Ehhhmmm...
– I only want people who praised Me and worshiped Me,
- Ben sadece Bana tapmış ve Beni övmüş insanları istiyorum,
and thanked Me when good things happened to them.
ve başlarına gelen iyilik için Bana şükretmiş olanları.
Preferably on national television.
Tercihen nasyonal televizyon'da.
– Sooo, why do you allow bad things to happen?
- Pekii, neden kötülüklere izin veriyorsun?
Even to Christians who love you.
Seni seven Hristiyanlara bile.
– I don’t have time for this nonsense!!
- Bu saçmalıklar için zamanım yok!!
I·I have prayers to listen to, and and
Be·Ben dualar işitmeliyim, ve ve
toasts to burn images of the Virgin Mary onto.
Hazreti Meryem'in resmini tostlara yakmalıyım.
I mean, I could be blessing America right now!
Yani şu an Amerika'yı kutsamakta olabilirim.
You·you can pick up a copy of My frequently asked questions from My asistancy here on your way out.
Se·Sen dışarıya çıkarken "sıkça sorulan sorular" kıtabı yardımcımdan alabilirsin.
– Where am I going?
- Neriye gidecem?
– Where do you think you’re going?!
- Ne sanıyorsun neriye gidecen?!
I hate to have to do this, but I am sending you to Hell!!
Bunu sevmeyerek yapıyorum, ama seni cehenneme yolluyorum!!
To burn in excruciating pain for eteernityyy!
Orada çekilmez azap içinde yanacan, soonsuzaa kadaar!
– Bu·but whyy?? I·I wasn’t a bad person at all.
- A·Ama nedeen?? Be·Ben hiç bir kötü insan değildim.
– You failed to believe in what I wrote about Myself in My best-selling book!
- Sen inanmadın o en çok satan kitabım'da kendim üzere yazdığım şeyleri!
You might as well have been a baby raper! Your fate would’ve been the same.
İsteseydin bir bebek tecavüzcü olabilirdin! Senin sonun aynısı olurdu.
– OK, I tell you what.
- Tamam, sana bir önerim var.
Let me return to earth for a day, so I can tell my loved ones that you really exist,
Beni bir günlük için dünya'ya koy, bana yakın olanlara söyleyimki sen gerçekten varsın,
and that they must worship and praise you, or else.
ve onlar sana tapsın ve seni övsünler, yoksa...
– NOOooo!!
- HAAayıır!!
They must learn the truth the same way everyone else does.
Onlar gerçeği aynen öbürler gibi kendileri öğrenmeliler.
Throough one of the many, questionably translated and edited versions
Heerhangı Benim bir kuşkulu cevirilmiş ve düzeltme ve
of My 2000-year-old collection of desert scribblings, an·and nothing more!
2000 sene yaşında olan eğri yazılar'dan, ve başka birşeyden değil!
Besides, your skull was totally crushed by that bus.
Ayrıca senin kafa tasın o otobüs'den tamamen ezilmişdi.
Bringing you back to life would be medically impossible, even by miracle standards.
Seni canlandırmak tıbben imkansızdır, mucıze standartlara göre bile.
There are some things I just cannot fix.
Öyle şeyler var ki, onları Ben düzeltebilemiyorum.
Remember that Terri Schiavo chick?
Terri Schiavo diye bir kız hatırlıyormusun?
There’s profound brain damage, amputated limbs, rabies...
Onda ağır beyin zararı, budanmış vücüd parçaları, kuduz vardı...
– Buut I thought you were...
- Amaa ben sandım sen...
– Silence!! You had your chance!
- Kes sesini!! Fırsatın vardı!
Hell is what people like you get for being skeptical of Me!
Senin gibi insanlar cehennemi bulurlar, Bana şüphe duydukları için!
Or for being born into a culture with the WRONG religion!
Veya bir kültüre doğmuş ve YANLIŞ dini benimsedikleri için!
And failing to find the path to Jesus Christ instead!
Ve onun yerine İsa'nın yolunu bulmadıkları için!
– Can I speak to someone else, like whoever made you?
- Başka birisiyle konuşabilirmiyim, mesela kim seni yaratmışsa?
– Goodbye non-Christian!!!
- Hoşçakal Hristiyan olmayan!!!
– NOOOOoooOoooOooo!
- HAAAyıııIıııIııır!
Let this be a warning to the rest of you!
Bu hepiniz için bir ibret olsun!
Worship and praise Me, the God of the Bible,
Bana tapın ve Beni övün, İncilin tanrısıyım,
or else!
yoksa!
BROUGHT TO YOU BY CHRISTIANS FOR THE PRAISING AND WORSHIPPING OF THE GOD OF THE BIBLE, OR ELSE.
SUNANLAR İNCİLİN TANRININ ÖVÜNMESİ VE TAPILMASI HİRİSTİYANLAR, YOKSA.
Subtitles: youtube.com/user/AlsanaAziz
Altyazılar: youtube.com/user/AlsanaAziz